

CONTACT

- +393481492867
- fabbian.alessandro@gmail.com
- Padua, Italy
- https://github.com/dalfabbio

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js
- Git, npm
- · Sass, Tailwind
- Problem solving
- · Project management
- Team working
- Team management
- Public speaking

LANGUAGES

- Italian (native speaker)
- English (C1)

INTERESTS

- Gaming
- Hiking
- Climbing
- Travelling

ALESSANDRO FABBIAN

FRONT-FND DFVFI OPFR

PROFILE

Psychologist with experience in project and team management, since 2022 I have enthusiastically dedicated myself to programming with a full stackoriented path. In every context I have worked in I have adopted a criticalanalytical approach to problem-solving, focusing on the end user. I am motivated by creating functional and optimized code, and I am looking for new opportunities to grow, progress and proactively contribute to the organizations I work with.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior front-end developer

JULY 2024 - PRESENT

UniPiazza SRL

- I have developed new features for the end user in ERP used by clients, built responsive layouts from the mockups provided by the web designer, and I took part in code reviews with the company's CTO.
- Skills: Git, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React for large-scale projects / teamwork / code review.

Local Service Manager

SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

Cooperativa Sociale Ancora

• Management and supervision of 95 people assisting disabled students in schools throughout the Padua area, managing communications with staff, school administrations, and public authorities.

Trainer and project planner

FEBRUARY 2020 - PRESENT

LAN association - (Cofounder)

· Participation in national call for proposal, networking, training of teenagers and young adults, planning of interventions on local scale, reporting.

Project Manager and Psychologist

APRIL 2019 - JUNE 2021

University of Padua / Humanitas Research Hospital Milano / IOV

· Pure and applied research activities, direct support to oncological patients, and management of communications between institutions.

EDUCATION

Start2Impact

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

- Full-stack development course
 - Projects built: [clickable links]:
 - Landing page (HTML, CSS, SASS): code demo • Tomato Counter (HTML, CSS, JS): code - demo
 - Discovery Library (HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JS, webpack, npm): code - demo

University of Padua

2010 - 2017

- Master Degree in Community Psychology (110/110 cum laude)
- Bachelor Degree in Psychological Sciences of Personality and Interpersonal Relationships

According to law 679/2016 of the Regulation of the European Parliament of 27th April 2016, I hereby express my consent to process and use my data provided in this CV and application for recruiting purposes.